Oh, somebody else is coming in.
Sorry.
Okay.
So, um, welcome.
Everyone's nice to see lovely faces.
Um, we wanted to do a call just because we haven't done a cam one for a while.
Um, so we wanted to just go over a few, uh, you know, a few ways that you can
sort of, um, build your business a bit more, um, get more clients in, find your
niche a little bit.
Um, if you just take one little bit of inspiration from, you know, this chat,
then that sort of thing, isn't it? And hopefully you girls, there's a few, a
few that are experienced, you can get some of your own pointers.
I have people to watch this back on their website and stuff.
Um, to watch out, do you want to say anything?
Um, yeah, just follow up on the call saying I hope that he's got something from
this. These are just things that I've used over the years and I'm sure
relatives here things as well. And maybe you've got things that we wouldn't
even think about.
Um, so if you want to add anything that's great for him.
Yeah.
Okay. Well, shall we just go through our points one by one and then we'll talk
about them a little bit and then, um, open it up and see if anyone else has got
any bits to add at the end of each point.
Yeah, sure.
Um, so the first thing that we talked about was having a good cam routine.
Yeah. Um, and what we mean by that is, um, obviously, um, being regular, so
having your own routine with the times that you can get on, I know that it's
harder for some people than it is for others is next.
Some people can only get on at certain times, but, um, it's how you build your
regulars, isn't it, by getting on consistently and at the same times if you can
.
Um, and also setting your availability on your, on your profile.
Um, so the people know when you're going to be on something actually that I'm
going to do because I've been a bit sporadic with it, because I've been so busy
.
I'm going to do that tonight. I'm going to go on and make sure I settle my
availability and keep myself accountable to those hours and I'm going on at
those times.
Um, and that's, it's also good to know, as well, when you're building your cam
routine, like, when are your busiest times, because we all have different
clients, like, for instance, my clients be very different from Georgia's.
Um, you know, my clients might come out at a different time of day that I get a
lot of older guys, um, which tends to come a lot on a Sunday.
Um, and Georgia is your stick. What, what sort of, what's your best or times
your best times for me.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's kind of changed now, like, living over here. It's like, it's like
all up in the air, but usually some days are great for me, not going to lie,
some days are really good, but I think some days are just good for everyone
because everyone's online on Sundays.
Um, but for me, the type of clients I actually prefer are daytime, you click UK
daytime clients, they're the type of clients I prefer because when it goes into
the evening.
The type of requests that I get don't really matter of what I like to, I like
to do. So that's what I worked out was best for me.
But then I know a lot of other girls stay thriving in the evening so yeah, yeah
, yeah, all different times and then you'll start to figure out what time to
best for you.
And that is good what you said there about this, you know what clients go on at
a certain time and what they want sort of thing that's really good said no isn
't it because then you're more inclined to stay on if you get in the clients
that you want if you're going on at the right time.
Yeah, I find that as well because I think in the early hours of the morning,
they're not really the times that I like call that like me that much or they
just want a quick hello and buy, which I don't really.
That's what I found that's why I like don't really do there was much time to do
if I'm you know available and just want to hop on and make a bit of action
money but yeah usually if I've got a choice.
I choose to do the daytime plans because they're a lot more more softer and not
so like, you know, after after they're all straight away.
Yeah.
Anything else on the camera to you.
Okay. So, yeah, like you said earlier about setting the work and hours.
When you said making yourself available, did you mean making yourself available
on the website or writing it on your profile because you can actually write it
on your profile to.
I don't know if you've somebody who's do this or not go in a lot of girls do
this the right so I don't choose it the first Monday this went to the second
Bible says, I have like next to it 10 a.m. To two p.m. Or whatever times they
're going to be online for that week.
And then the clients know what time they're going to get them.
So that's something good to do and obviously if you do it like you need to
stick to it because if you put it on there and then show up on them times.
Your clients are going to see that because they will actually see that you've
said you're going to be on that time and you're welcome to see you at that time
so that's something you can do.
And I also wanted to talk about maybe a self care slash empowerment exercise
you can do before you go online.
One of our members and she actually spoke about this because I didn't, I never
used to do this. And she spoke about it on one of the calls in recently.
She likes to moisturize a whole body and we're paying for you. Obviously that's
completely for the self snuff of the clients to see or enjoy because they can't
feel a gorgeous moisturized skin or smell how she smells she does that for
itself.
In like the right state to come in and like love herself and feel good about
herself. So that's something you could maybe do before going on canvas.
Always have a little routine or a little something you like to do to get
yourself into the mood and.
I just interrupt you just quickly. Yeah sure go ahead.
Under my pillow to look you can see here where it actually even is the tube.
Can you see that? I know I before like if it's later on and then I take all my
like so I put a bit of makeup on and then later on I take it all off and just
do like more like just cozy coming.
But I put this all over my body.
It's called liquid towel it's like baby towel which is really weird but I just
feel like all cozy and then I'm like I just leave my light on really low and
just do like a few late night calls and that's exactly what I do use that but
it all over my body makes me feel good.
Nice, nice. Do you know what that's a good point as well when you're thinking
about a camera routine is that you can have different areas or different moods
for different days and times you go on so like you said like when it gets later
at night you might change the light in a bit or something.
And it helps you, doesn't it and makes you feel a bit more like bit less like
my little wind down time but I still am happy to take a few causes especially
from like regulars that I know they're going to be on late but they just want
to have a little chat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, thank you for that.
Yeah, go on Georgia.
I think I've got one more to talk about.
So, oh yeah so I also wanted to talk about when you're doing the camera routine
not forcing yourself to go online when you're not feeling it.
Like the interactions to your clients they're going to see you and obviously
you can't pull from an empty cup so if you're just not feeling it.
And you're just you know you said that you're going to go on but you really not
feeling it maybe it's just best not to just like just give yourself the night
off, because you could go online for example and that might not even be busy
and then it might make you feel even worse.
And so yeah just know like how you feel and in the moment and like if you
really not feeling it then it's just not worth doing it you know I mean, but
then on the flip side they totally like contradicts or whatever said.
Sometimes you might not be feeling so good and I go online and be very busy and
I'm really nice clients and make a lot of money so it's one of them you still
need to worry about am I in the right mind setting to do this now and if it
even if it is dead and we're still going to feel okay you know.
That's something to consider is when you're thinking about your cam routine
just not forcing yourself like if you're just not feeling in the moment,
because it might just put you off a life you know you might go on one time you
're not feeling good and then have a shit time on cam and then you might just
be like I'll just can't be doing it anymore you know.
So yeah just not worth it just for that one time.
That's me I've been eva when we were at this shoot and I just shoved my cam on
and I just like was just chatting one minute and I shut my cam on and there's
some calls coming through and I was just like chatting or whatever.
And he was like oh my god I make like such a big effort for calm like like
being proper sensual and having all the hair and make when everything.
Sometimes you can just shove it on can't you that's the beauty of it that you
might just be busy just sit there and just shove it on a minute and without
thinking too much.
I've been learning to do that a little bit more and we've been a bit I've been
really busy at the moment but and as soon as I finish this course I can get
back into this again.
Thank you for that day I just realised I'll just like I will come in on like I
don't know that panel around and this and I don't even need to be palmer like
just be there.
I think sometimes I prefer it when you're not when you're not all massively
done up like this is what you've got but most of mine prefer me in like little
pink pyjamas and like looking sort of cute or whatever not.
Not, not all.
If it is a weekend and I know that certain people aren't going to be on then I
will think I'll put some underwear on or whatever but most of the time I just
wear my pyjamas and I do alright with that so.
I have to look like it's nice to do it sometimes for yourself as well but you
don't always have to be like completely polished I don't think.
Yeah, and I think I was thinking about that because I was thinking it's good to
have a camera routine like it's good to have a routine before you go on to like
cite yourself up getting the mood whatever.
You don't always need it sometimes it's like just take a look at that top see
panels there you know I do like this I'll do it like this in between like
working the day sometimes and be like oh I'll just see panels there and
sometimes they are.
Yeah, yeah definitely I think that what I've noticed a lot of them, a lot of
girls obviously in the beginning the ask a lot of questions and they don't
really.
Like the worry if like you have to do all this effort and where this and where
that and then I tell them like yeah you can do that that's going to make you
feel good and step into your character but it's also like you really don't have
to do that like we've just said it's like you
really don't have to it's not this big this big like thing that you have to
show up to every time like in this sit and look you can just go on as yourself
one day and just see how that works.
And also it's got it's got to be something if you want to get online regularly
it's probably something that you can and can do regularly isn't it.
You want to go on and every time you take into hours to get ready then of
course you're going to feel a bit like you asked.
Yeah that would be a bit much.
So that's all I have to say about on that one round having a good cam routine.
I'm not sure if you had any foot left on there. We'll go on to the next one.
Yeah I think that's it really isn't that. Yeah. Okay.
So do you want to go.
Yeah sure so we were going to talk about how to get people into your chat.
So first thing that wants to mention was from page. I'm sure all of you here
probably know what that is but I'll just explain it quickly to people who are
watching it back.
You can you can be able to put yourself onto the front page the website.
And when you're on the front page for me, mainly I do get a lot more calls than
when I'm not.
So recommend that it's got to try it and if you ask in one of the mentors we
can help you how to do this.
But yeah that's a good thing to try because there's loads of girls online at
one time and if you're on the front.
Usually it means you might get more likely to get more calls.
And another thing you could do if you don't pay the front page but want to be
noticed on the first page is you can turn on your free chat.
So usually it's not turned on when you sign up with us but we can't turn it on
and show you how to do it yourself so you can just flick it on and off whenever
you like.
And yeah the free chat usually puts you on the front page doesn't it when you
do free chat.
Of course when I do that usually like you usually get on the front you don't
have to pay for it but it's usually you have to pay.
Sorry for the girls who don't know this.
And yeah in free chat you can tempt guys to take it into a paycheck so that's
another way to get people into your chat room in free chat they're just going
to come in non stop so that's a really fast like like guaranteed way to get
people in.
So another way to get people into your chat is to have an eye catching profile
and my kitchen profile picture one thing as well.
Most you might know this but maybe some of you don't is really like crop the
profile picture in so there's no wasted space so for example if my box now, as
you can see me as my profile picture, I wouldn't be like super super far away
because
all this here for the sides.
It's just getting wasted that you want to be quite close.
And like, so I probably do my profile picture like this guy for example, like
this angle if I was doing one now because most of me takes up the screen.
Because when you're a little icons on the on the big screen of all the girls if
you're not really occupying a full space of your photo it's not going to show
as much so that's another little tip that I learned over the years was to.
Crap out the rest of the profile and just have you like whatever your picture
is on it.
This probably like you know there's obviously the odd occasion where other
pictures might be my kitchen or whatever else for usually that's what that's
what I think is best.
So I liked it when one of the girls hopes about him that she changes it every
time she goes online that's something I never used to do but I do do that now.
And I actually noticed that the guys doing the details of it so we definitely
do look at the strap line before they come here and what you wrote in yours
might just be the difference of whether they are interested to come here or not
.
And so yeah there's my tips on how to get people in to the room.
And you can you can put on your strap line and something that you're going to
talk about when they're in the chat with you like something to do with what you
're wearing or something that you've experienced or something that you're
thinking about today.
And it's like a teaser of what they can get if they come into the house and
then you can have a bit of a story for something to talk about rather than just
cleaning it.
Lisa, yeah, do you hand up, you put your hand up, did you want to ask a
question.
Yeah hi yeah I just I'm new to this I've only been on it for a week or so.
But I wanted to ask you know where you say about you can pay to go on to the
front page and it comes up I haven't really, I've tried to look at the whole
the whole thing and try and sort of get to know the actual site and you know
trying to go through it all
So how do you actually it comes up with times and do you have to pay to get on
to the front like how does that actually work.
Yeah, yeah, so it does I think it does show you in our welcome course in our
beginners course isn't it Georgia on our website.
Yeah it sort of walks you through how to do it.
And you pay by the hour in credit.
We do have a video on it actually don't we.
We do have a video on it.
I'll direct you to the video Lisa after him after the call.
But yeah it's quite simple and once you've done it once or twice you'll you'll
remember how to do it.
And that's sorry is that the link that you sent me Georgia.
For where we've got the link to see the videos because I've just been winging
it really looking at the whole website and just doing my thing and I mean, like
I said to you today I've done okay for two days that I did actually do it.
So I've been winging it so I don't really know the ins and outs, but I don't
know those videos.
Okay, yeah I just went on to our chat just to check and I did at the very start
of the chat I sent you in to sign up to our members area don't if you remember
you did sign up and I accepted your.
So I'll recent you the website you can just log in it's our website it's
nothing to do with the website that you come on it's just purely for your girls
.
So you can log in and on there you can access all of the training in videos all
of the training articles, and there's a welcome course which is good for new
started to do.
Sorry, is that the ECC working camera device on that.
It's not on my chat it's on a chat with you but I'm just going to send you it
now because I literally just went on to it just to check that I did send you it
so I just send you it now.
And yet you registered with our members area so with it using even passwords if
you don't remember it I can log in and find it for you.
And it's on the welcome course on week one, and there's a video to show you
exactly how to do the front page.
So I think the member is you have to in bids about five minutes to the hour you
have to do it about five minutes to. So if you want to go online at nine p.m.
You don't want to do it like hours before you want to do it at five to nine.
I think the main thing to remember really just do a five minutes before the
hour.
Right okay and I'll just click on to that and there's a door I have to put in a
password did you say.
Yeah so click on what I've just sent you if you click on members area, then it
should ask you to use name and password that you registered with.
Okay so when I log on.
It's the same one with it when I log on.
It's not the Jessica rabbit one it's whatever you signed up to our website with
but I'm going to go on to the website out of this for you and remind you of
what it was.
Right fantastic thank you.
No worries.
Yeah it's definitely worth doing that welcome course for anyone that hasn't
done it even as a refresher because you know even when I've been back and
looked at it I've been like oh yeah.
And I've read on it all now so it's not, it's a bit of a mumbo jumbo in the
last one because I didn't like finalize it all but yeah it's all been finalized
now and it's like a quiz and stuff so in.
Yeah it's a little bit better than it was now I think like the layout and stuff
like that.
Can I ask as well do you think it's better to, I didn't know it's better to
beat before like five to the hour for position in.
Yeah, see because when you do it when you do it like you know half an hour 20
minutes or whatever before whatever goes before.
Yeah, see when you do it before it can go say for example it goes green on free
credits and and then you get to like five to nine or whatever time it is.
Maybe it's gone off to four credits because more people are busy.
So obviously I do mine in advance so if I, because I know like at the moment
like 10 o'clock's really quiet.
So I like, because I'm calm at that time every night like two days or the day
before I'll always be like well not always but I do bid and pay like two three
credits.
Do you find that I'm on the first page is that why because that's why then you
should be.
Yeah, I have to bid at about five parents about five credits every time I found
a trip.
Yeah, if you want to be if you want to be the top of the first page you did
five five oh one or five oh two, it guarantees you the first three or four rows
on the front page.
If you bid five I found myself on the second page before doing that if you bid
five on average I'm just saying I found I've got a bid at least five five at a
maximum I'd say to get on the front page.
Sammy saying.
Oh, that's brilliant. Thank you.
Yeah, six.
Yeah, I think it just depends on the times that when our busy is on you know
how many girls are busy and five six could be like usually what it is both
sometimes in the daytime for me for example because I go on in the UK day times
like I said.
In four credits could be from page.
And then if I'm feeling like a bit generous and I made a bit of good good money
but I'll put in if it goes green on four, like I said Tory you can put in a
little bit more.
I just put in also credit more or one credit more. Yeah.
Then you guarantee like the very top of the front page. So that's a good thing.
If you know if you're working if you're making money on there and they can
watch me out I'll put an extra credit.
I have a quick question and Georgia was to put you a minute.
Yeah.
The visit what's the difference between featuring and positioning.
I think featuring my profile and I find all days much cheaper obviously when
you know that example on Thursday you're gonna you've got lots of time like few
hours, good few hours, like on the morning and on the evening.
This works for me much better because it's much cheaper I always put ticks
credit every hour and they're like a day I think it's like only 12, 13 credits.
So it is better and you sit on the front page and it's the same.
So it would be far better to feature than it would position if you know you're
going to be available that day.
The further you do it in advance the further you feature in advance the lower
it's there so you can do it's like a couple of weeks in advance if you know
when you're going to be online and it can be like a little of six credits or
something for the whole day.
So yeah, remember that starts 12 at the midnight so the whole actually night
and whole day, so like one hour one day and a half isn't it.
That's a lot.
Yeah, that's right actually now you've reminded me I'm going to do that for
Sunday because I plan to come all day Sunday so yeah I'll probably feature for
Sunday.
It is much cheaper. Yeah. Yeah, I'm going to give it a go as well. I'm going to
give it a go because I've never actually done it myself so that's why I don't
have, I don't have any knowledge on it so I've never done it but I just hear
what you girls tell me and stuff.
So I'm going to give that a go as well so yeah I'm still bringing that one up
because maybe it'll be the best like new thing for me and for all of us.
But not new for you because you could you do it but yeah the one you haven't
done it yet. Let's report back we'll report back next week.
Yeah, definitely, definitely.
Something I really wanted to do as well was feature but I just didn't know how
to do it or like what, how it worked or anything so it's good to know that.
Do you know where it is Sam made you know I'll do it. Yeah, I do know but I
didn't know what the times were and like how it actually worked and stuff
because I don't.
But because I do plan ahead then I could definitely do that so I know the day
and I saw it. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's true. So maybe feature them will be good for people who plan ahead
and then just the front page hour to hour is probably better than the people I
don't.
It's better if you're going on for a lot in one way, like if you're on for a
few hours and one day isn't it rather than the power.
Okay.
Okay, so that was getting clients in.
Also we talked said mentioned about the profile didn't you I think like the
profiles massive isn't it it's what captures their eye if they're going to come
with you or not.
Not just having big blocks of writing like having spaces in between maybe some
capital letters some emojis like something that makes it stand out so they're
lazy aren't they makes it easier to read.
And they can see exactly what you're into and what you do.
And, and I always say when I'm like got new girls I always say like what makes
you you like or if it's not you your alter ego you know what I mean.
Oh there you go Sammy.
Yeah so having something a bit more personal that just because you know your
your profile is talking to the client that you want to have it's an invitation
to the client that you want isn't it so if you're just saying big tips juicy
ass whatever
that's the client that you're going to get and that's what you're going to
expect but if you're saying that comment I talk about like my like that I'm a
professional and this is what I enjoy I'm into fetish I like this and that I
like to take control or
give control I like I give a lot more detail about me as a person and why I'm
different from other people and I think that's good to have.
Yeah, definitely 100% and with the profile as well.
And the thing that one of the first things you see when you're just on the page
of everybody else is in feedback.
So the more feedback you've got the more established the profile looks and
maybe the more likely they'll be to come but saying that also in the very
beginning when you know you don't have any.
I think that's a bit of a unique selling point as well because there's not
there's not always loads of new girls there's only a small amount of new girls
compared to how many girls that aren't new.
So if you are new like yourself Lisa and you don't have any feedback and stuff
like that yes that's still absolutely fine.
Why are you building up to where and could you can play on the new cards as
well because some of them like the fact well, a lot of them like the fact that
you knew.
And you can be like oh this is my first time you know it's exciting you show me
the ropes and stuff like that so that's something you can play on.
But yeah with the feedback.
It's definitely good to work towards building up feedback and because it is one
of the first things that clients say when you're just on the page about
everybody else and to do this.
So you're trying to leave your feedback so if you're you know having a chat
with someone and you know it's, it's a lengthy one it's not just a quick high
buy kind of thing.
You can say towards the end as the chat's coming to an end you can say
something like.
I'm trying to build up my feedback you can even say you know me and other girls
are trying to have a competition who can get the most this week or you know
stuff like that and I really appreciate if you let me a feedback.
You can say that to them, or if you don't get the chance to say that you can
just leave on yourself for them.
And hopefully they'll see that and leave you on back.
That's another thing to consider when doing the profile is getting as much.
And if you if you click if you log in and click on to your messages.
And it automatically tells you what feedback you need to give doesn't it tells
you who you come with and teach to the screen where you can give them feedback
so always giving them feedback because then sometimes they come and give you
some back.
Yeah definitely and I just put your profile off there on more pages.
If you're given all these different clients feedback you're appearing on their
pages too you know and I mean, yeah it's just good to get your profile off
there as much as possible more advertising.
And I think it's good to remember not to feel stuck with your profile like just
experiment with it all the time.
I'm like I've built mine now the way I like it and so I only make little tweaks
now and again but it took me a long time to find my like niche and my profile
that I really like.
And like I went through loads of different, one stage I was a nurse.
Went through loads of different things that I thought I would like and that
works at the time or that just moved on so it kind of grows with you doesn't it
.
Yeah, definitely. Okay, so the next thing we're going to talk about keeping
clients in so you've got clients into your room and then it's about keeping
them in as in it which some people can feel a bit stuck on.
And actually that sort of thinking maybe and I was talking to George about
calls we're going to do in February but I was thinking at some point of doing
like fantasy building call, like a Zoom call where we sort of all have a
template and sort of create
build on together our own fantasies that we can have to chat to guys about on
cam.
And that's something that I do massively I have a few scenarios in my head real
or imagined or that I've found inspiration from other things and I just go
through them, like I've said before just line by line given them little tip
bits and
it's always it's pretty much always starts with the conversation of when I'm
going to meet them.
And that's a good thing to remember that when clients are asking you to meet.
Like a good percentage of the time it's just a fantasy and that's an invitation
to actually go to a lengthy conversation and bring them into a fantasy and
potentially make a lot of money.
I think a lot of girls get put off by like oh my god no I'm not going to meet
but actually a lot of that is fantasy.
And it's really time consuming.
And it can give you good regulars like I have the same regulars, some of the
same regulars I've had for years and we talk about this meat we're going to
have every single time like twice a week.
It's clearly not going to happen and it's easy because I just say the same
thing pretty much each time so they're the best ones aren't they can be boring
sometimes but like only a lot of money.
Yeah, do you want to say. Yeah, sure. So, um, so keeping the clients in the
room so you want to show interest and obviously remember that the pain you buy
the minute to talk to you.
So give them your attention. One thing that I was definitely guilty of in the
beginning, I didn't really give it me for attention I'd be doing other things
and whatever else and you just slip away.
So when I, or even now still sometimes if I'm busy and I love on Cam just, and
I'm like getting things from them in between. It doesn't really, I don't really
do well but if I'm given them my full attention and I put my attention out onto
them.
Yeah, you're just willing to give them the attention because that's what the
day for you know the meal with it to chat yeah, because at the end of the day
if you just wanted to see a beautiful woman, you know, in a beautiful form.
They would just go on to a porn website or something like that. You want to get
to know you and they want to talk to you so yeah just give them the attention.
Another thing that I want to talk about that I always say it's like my little
trick that I do to get clients into private and it does work like most of the
time.
So if we're in group chat and you know we're just you know a little chat
whatever like see what what what with each other.
I just always say them in the face couple of sentences I just always say do you
have a camp and then most of the time. Yeah, and then I just say, oh let's go
to private and we can see to see like come to come.
And for anyone who doesn't know what that means and it just means open there
come as well. So when you first log on and when they first come into your chat
you can't see them, but then you can open request to open their camp.
And that works for me all the time and they just say okay then yeah let's do it
. So then just got them into private so easily and it's not like I'm, you know,
having to promise that I'm going to do something for private or anything like
that you know like I'll take me to private and I'll do this or whatever else.
It's just oh yeah I'll open you come and private. And if they ask why I don't
open it in group chat I just tell them because there's so many guys in group I
've known you open one at a time.
So it's not fair on the other so let's just take me to private and you've got
my attention nobody else has so that's one little thing I do and that works for
me all the time and it's just really simple things to say.
And another thing about keeping the clients in the room as well is having a
clear and good quality webcam and good lighting.
We mention this all the time but it's it's very like important.
So if you could be like the perfect scale for them like exactly who they want
to be coming all the time.
But if they can't see you or you know the lightens no good or the cameras no
good then they're not going to stay around because it's just going to be very
expensive for them just to see like a really crappy image that they can't
actually see you know.
So I think really nailing the lighting and the and your webcam is a really
important one for keeping clients in.
And yeah another thing to keep in the clients in, keep it not really sure where
to go or to take the conversation.
We have questions that we send to all of you at the start when you first
enjoying if anyone doesn't have it just message either of us and we'll send you
a just a list of like open questions that you can ask the clients.
And then maybe you'll ask a question and it'll take the combo down a path that
you never thought it would go and hopefully it'll be a lengthy path that makes
you a lot of money.
So anybody else have any tips on this because I'm sure some of you girls like,
you know, might have you do a lot of things or no.
Okay.
But you think about as well as now.
I think it's good to have like I mentioned before like a little tip bit a
little story like this is my sort of prep before I go on camera think okay what
what like what happens day what can I make a fantasy out of.
Or even just a little funny story out of like, always say like, like I said
before like all the postman's been today and we've got this little thing going
on like I know I know he wants me type of thing.
Like just like a little just a little tip little scenario where if the
conversation is a bit stuck or whatever you can be like.
All right, came online because I was thinking about this or this person in work
or this happened in the shop earlier like something a bit like teasing and a
bit and a bit like 30 or whatever.
So yeah it's good to have a little something in your mind I think before you go
on because then you know you're not going to get stuck.
And it's good in group as well because if you're talking to a few people at a
time you usually get a bit of stuff back from people and then it just takes it
in your direction.
Yeah, I usually try and find out like within the first or five minutes what
that person's into because I do everything from like adult breastfeeding spl
ashing to blooming you know girlfriend experience type thing on cam so it could
be anything so I like to try and narrow it down so I know which part of myself
I need to be working does that make sense.
Yeah, yeah yeah totally yeah not being afraid to ask questions like don't
assume that you know or that you can't ask questions we can all ask questions
actually that's really yeah so I just say like what's your pink or fetish you
know and if they're like oh I'm a real
babe sky then I know I've got to work my boobs you know on this call that's I'm
gonna tease and that will keep them on you know.
Yeah and being just staying curious I think like sometimes people put pressure
on themselves to know everything or to be performing or whatever but actually
curiosity is so undervalued like if you're just curious about what they like
and who they are and how their days
have been and you know what's going on for them then that that can take you
somewhere unexpected that can be like a lengthy call on it.
Yeah, yeah definitely.
I've got a really good, if you hear me I don't know if you know on my phone I
've got a really good tip for cam to come.
So if you're come to come in with someone who is repulsive and doing something
is that not something that you really want to look at.
So there's a great tip I was told about putting a post it now on your on your
laptop screen so you can't actually see what they're doing because it's hard
sometimes to look at them, but not face pressure.
I've got one better than that. So what I've done so I love Jason my mama. So I
've got a picture of him out and I've stuck his face and body to when it's like
this really fat guy can like bounce it up and down on a deal down or something.
You can see that I'm doing this. So I stick it over the screen but it looks
like I'm staring at him with always wanting.
That's a good idea. Yeah, not the night like that wins it. That's the tip of
the night.
Yeah, the other night I have to watch some guy put sounding rods up his japs I
have his witty and I couldn't look and I was just trying to point the camera
down and it kept saying, Oh, can I want to see your face I want to see your
reaction and I'm just like bloody hell.
Wow.
I'm pretty open minded but that was just for something else.
I don't feel like yourself and it's like, oh, yeah, I don't like to look at
that.
Yeah, that's a really good tip.
And what I always do is I always turn my volume right down. The minute I do
come to come with someone I turn my volume right down because I don't mind
looking at things I just don't want to hear, don't want to hear things.
I'm not hearing people breathing or anything.
I can hear a reflection of myself sometimes you need self can't you and it's
like, Oh, go on, mix it a bit more for your land. Yeah.
That's the best, Sammy. Thank you for sharing that one.
Lisa, did you act to your question.
Yeah, there was a couple of times there's, I've noticed there's one particular
guy that keeps coming on.
And he says some light is a complete idiot and I straight away I tried to block
him.
And I think it's like he knows like that I'm going to block him so I'll go to
block him and then suddenly he goes straight off.
I'm going to come back on on trying to do the permanent block.
But it doesn't block him is I don't know he just comes off very quickly.
He says whatever he's got to say and then he literally goes off.
So I don't have I'm literally on it straight away going block block permanently
block and and then I don't get a chance to do it.
It just doesn't work.
Sorry, is it is it terrible what he says.
Just some like nasty comment also me because even a friend of mine she's on on
here as well and she's new to it and she we obviously speak about certain guys
that the names that come up and she's like Oh my gosh, I have him and I tried
to block him and he comes off straight away
like and she goes I don't get a chance to block him.
It comes at guest and then a number I'd have to log it down.
Yeah, it will be on your credit statement.
If you join your room it will be on your credit statement.
So we'll take a look after this after the call or tomorrow or some fun and
maybe we can report them to the help desk and ask the help desk.
Can you please block him from my profile. I'm not sure I've never done that
before but both both try as the help desk for you.
And yeah, just so you know as well Lisa I know you're new to this.
So maybe you think that's normal. That's not really normal. It does happen
sometimes, but it doesn't happen all of the time you've only been on twice
having you.
So for that, that's not going to happen. It's a cast because you can enable
gusts on your, where are we putting the five minutes in 24 or just worse and
there is the, there you can pick the cast isn't there.
Yeah.
You can allow, you can allow guests or not, can't you? So you can pick that
beat to ask.
But that's only on free chat though, isn't it? That's on free chat if you can
enter. Are you, are you using free chat as well Lisa?
Yeah, I go on free chat for a while.
We're on tick guests because I think as well, like for anyone who's listening
to badness. I don't think it's good to have guests ticked on free chat because
it means that people who aren't even registered on the site can can come you.
And if they don't even register on the site, they've got no credits because
they haven't even gotten a countable credit in so so you don't want the guests
looking at you because they're not the ones who are spending anyway.
And clearly, you can say in nasty things so, you know, be in trouble.
So yeah, we will untick guests.
Will you do that for me, Georgia?
I'll do that straight away.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, that makes sense. Yeah. So definitely if they're not actually a member,
definitely don't want to be dealing with those guys, especially with what they
come up with.
Yeah, that's not nice. I'm sorry about that.
Okay, no, that isn't normal. It's a girls like sometimes don't get me wrong.
But normally you have done it. It only happens a handful of times. If that's
happened in your face.
You probably think and fuck this is going to happen all the time, but it really
shouldn't. It really doesn't usually.
I don't think I've ever had that, you know, I don't think I've ever had that in
years.
I just put it down to just, it's just a man in general. So I don't take offence
to it, but it's more like on blocking your straight away.
You don't like energy.
Right. You're not getting away with that.
No, I can't.
Yeah.
Away. And I just like, no, you find the block here.
But yes, it's a lot harder.
As soon as I noticed that you could guess could come off and off in, I turned
that off straight away.
You'd like, George says, they're not going to pay you to do anything.
So there's no point even entertaining them.
The ones that guy was asked later, he come back with his real username.
And he said that we just spoke. I said, when he said that he was a guest. So I
don't know how this works, but he was nice.
It's just, I don't know. Sometimes they can go like two or five. So I don't
know.
Maybe I'll have to add a bit more, but yeah, I think the guests usually are the
ones that don't have credit, you know, so don't even want to entertain them
once.
Because in free chats, a lot of them can be freeloaders anyway, never mind if
the guests, they'd definitely freeloaders. So we definitely want to cut that
out.
Yeah, it's actually great. Thank you.
Sorry, did you want to say something?
Yeah, I did. If that's all right. I just wanted to ask, I don't know if you.
I've not heard us touch on this much, but I think I mentioned it's one of the
girls today.
I was saying we're talking about traffic into AdultWork. So I'm on Reddit,
Twitter, OnlyFans, TikTok, Insta. So my, my account on this AdultWork, I've
got accounts for my, you know, alter ego on different platforms.
And it seems it does help bring more traffic into AdultWork. I just wondered
what other people are doing to bring more traffic in to a W.
Yeah, good question. And you can link up your Twitter, can't you, which is.
And also there's a link, you can get the link direct link to your profile. Can
't you from my details page that you can post on other sites as well.
Yeah, does anyone does anyone use other sites to promote and think it helps
them.
Yeah, me, but I just don't have no time to doing this. But when I started doing
this, when I started with you in November, I noticed that I had few items from
Instagram, for example, and one guy from Twitter.
I'm new on Twitter anyway. So, yeah, I just, at the moment, don't have time,
but probably if you, some energy into, I think we'll have.
Yeah.
I think it's a really helps, doesn't it?
What do you do with you?
Yeah.
Well, I do do Twitter, but I'm not actually allowed to do it myself because
they banned me now. So,
somebody runs it for me because I can't log into my phone because when I do the
link that IP address, but I do have one.
But yeah, with Twitter, it's more like sex with sex workers will promote
themselves on Twitter because, well, I say it a lot more friendly for that.
But I actually got banned off of that, but it usually is a lot more friendly
when it comes to sex with with his Instagram.
They're a lot more strict. So you can still get away with it. But, but yeah,
you're going to be careful on these platforms now because
a lot of them are starting to not allow like promotion of sex with.
So you just got to be careful with it. One thing you can do is don't put the
link on your page, like in the buyer, anything like that.
Just say DM me for the link. A lot of girls do that. And that's what I do as
well.
I think it's not as well.
Yeah, I mean, it's safe to not have the link in your bio, but as it were,
anything like that.
What you could do is you could make an all links or a link tray or something
like that. I think the calls and it's basically a website header thing.
And then you've got all your links in it. So it's in your bio. It doesn't say
like adaweck.com slash whatever you, you know, your fingers.
It's like a link to the link and then your other works and that would make even
a step further, a bit more safer to not be deleted off the platforms.
It's just say DM me for the link and then they send a link and you don't reply
again on there.
You just wait until leave because then they'll try and message it on there, of
course, and you don't want to give them the message for break.
Well, yeah, I think using other platforms is it can be a great way to get
clients in if you're using them and regular on it and got a following on there.
Like people actually, you know, you actually point energy into it, then people
start to follow you on there and then follow you over on to add up work and
stuff.
So can definitely be a thing if you've got the time to do that.
You have to be careful, though, don't you, because I gave my, because I use
kick to talk to regulars to tell them when I'm coming online and blah, blah,
blah.
And this guy, he actually just wanted to create content with me, which I always
check out first, because I've had a few guys that are legit and a few guys that
aren't, but it was like content for adult works.
And because I gave, because I mentioned kick, I got a warden.
The thing that makes me die is that I use kick to, like, literally, like say
something very ugly, it's like, Oh, I've been tonight, like, or like send them
like a cheeky picture and then be like, I'll be on at nine o'clock tonight and
they'll always come online and always talk to me so they'll always
be going to profit from me doing that.
Yeah, I've got a bloody warning for it.
And then really strict on mentioning any other sites on there.
I don't make money out of adult works at all. It's just, it's just like them to
be like, Oh, come on, like, sexy time.
I know, and it is good that you're able to do that and, you know, keep up with
that as much as you can.
But yeah, telling people on group or private chat or emails or any, but you've
got different platforms. So the thing is, like, you can't give out your
platforms, like the people are following your on them face and they go into
your other work.
Then you've already got there, they contact that way, but you can't give them
out because it happened to Sophie as recently as actually.
And she get out something that she wasn't meant to and she got a warning and if
the art on it, you really are on it because I'm so stupid though, because
actually, I get quite a lot of work from doing that.
And then like all the work goes straight for adult works anyway, don't get it
privately.
Yeah, see, it's so ridiculous.
I know, you're doing it the way you are that that's fine because, like you said
, you're giving them all, like, you're taking the money through them anyway, but
other girls will just message them on kick and say, let's just do a Skype
session and I'll charge unless or whatever I don't know.
And then they might charge a little bit, but then how do they, how do they pay
them.
So that you can't put your paper on paper, you can pay your own paper or bank
transfer or cash. That's illegal though paper to do that.
You can go to prison for that.
I always use cash out and go some money for stuff.
Oh, see, I'm stupid. I'll do any of that. I don't give up my bank details.
I'm like, no, guys, that works.
Yeah.
And that's the best way to do it because where you're not going to get your
profile deleted and I've said to, like, the girls, it's probably not worth it
for that little bit of money that you're going to make outside.
That's why I get annoyed, because I give my kick out, like, or like I say, I'll
talk to me on kick because I find it easier to just be like, Oh, I'm in the
bath.
Like, I'll be on in half an hour.
And then they'll come straight to AdultWork. So they're like, I learn money.
Food's like exactly how I should do through the system. Like, I'd never ever do
any private money transactions.
I do everything for adult works, but it is that just that little bit of like,
Oh, like, this is what I'm wearing tonight.
Do you like it? Or should I change? And I do that through kick and then I've
got, I've got a warning for it.
Yeah.
There's no way around that, unfortunately, Sammy, it will be.
I suppose to them, they just think I'm taking money. And I'm honestly not.
I tell you what it's about.
Like, I just think you're like, you have girls, Sammy, like, that's what the
majority of girls will do, obviously.
Yeah.
Yeah. See, on the part of your profile, you can like add your Twitter and
everything on.
And there is a place for kick to put kick you the name.
There's a name.
Yeah.
There's what you can have a lot of things on board.
Because I don't like to use Twitter or Twitter or Instagram because obviously I
've got teenage sons.
So I have to be really careful. Whereas with kick, like, he would never even
know what that bloody was.
You know, I mean, like, I've looked on it. And, but all you can do is I don't
know where you find it on your actual profile.
Because I've added my Twitter and everything, but I can't see it on my profile.
Oh, we're looking to it. Well, that's the help desk. And we're looking to that
maybe tomorrow, girls.
I figure that one out because even if you can put one link on there, even if it
's just Twitter.
Yeah.
Even if it's just Twitter.
It's making them money as well. So, you know, like, anyone's skimming anyone
out of anything.
So, yeah.
It's on the general section of the profile.
If you go to general when you're on your laptop, scroll down and then it's just
manage apps and you just start everything in there and then just view it
afterwards.
Yeah. Okay. Thank you.
Yeah. If you allow you to do that, then that's going to be fine writing it in
the messages. That's where you get a bit of it.
Even saying out loud they can be funny with it.
Yeah.
Okay.
When you give it out in the thing, unless you're on a phone chat thing, you
know, when you're doing it.
No, I give mine out because I ask us as well. So, I have to give mine out.
Yeah, see, that doesn't add to contact me.
Yeah. Yeah. If you're being booked and stuff like that, then that's okay.
But just in your group or private chat, if you give it out there, they don't
like that either.
Yeah, it's like, it's like you've got to just go around the way, like you've
got the rules, but then there's ways you can get around it if you do it this
way, but not that way, you know, so yeah.
Okay. Thank you.
Okay. Thank you, ladies.
There's lots of good stuff there.
We're going to run to the next, the next.
There was just a couple more things we're going to talk about was about like
finding your niche.
And knowing your clients. So knowing the type of clients that are going to want
to come with you and that you're going to want to come with as well.
It's always good idea to kind of bring some of yourself some of your own
interest, your own hobbies, your own things that you like and to come so that
it's less of a chore.
And also to experiment with with different things, I say, like different looks
and different times that you go on different styles like different things you
can wear.
And, you know, you might want to try like submissive or dominant and kind of
experimenting with things because I think some people think are a bit sort of
put off by thinking that they have to be an expert in something to do it.
But most of the time guys love you experimenting and sort of trying something
new, whether it's been dominant or submissive or a different fetish anything.
And so I think, yeah, it's great to experiment, isn't it, and not not to feel
stuck in the one thing that you're doing at the moment there's always other
things.
And you can look at other people's profiles for inspiration or even just asking
the chats and things because we all do sort of different things and have
different personalities on there.
Or even like, you know, building your character on cam, like I said before,
like I used sales and nurse and then I had a couple of other like things that I
would say about myself.
And but I would even take inspiration from like people that I like on Instagram
like women that I looked up to I'll be like oh yeah she's cool what does she do
what she like and just take bits of their personality and make it into my own
on cam.
They stuff that they were posting about and talking about I'll start talking
about it to clients and just giving it a bit of a sexy edge.
And so this like there's inspiration everywhere isn't there.
And yeah, anything else on that Georgia.
And I think you mentioned a lot more like a couple of points that I need but
mainly like what feels good to you and what doesn't so where the feels good
like you said just explore the further.
And because like I said something that you never thought you could be
interested in you might actually be and then be really good at it and shock
yourself so like you don't have to have all the knowledge like well said on it.
And you can just give it a go and then you might really love it and then expand
your knowledge on it and get better at it.
And, and finally, don't do anything you're not completely comfortable with
obviously we talk about this a lot, it'll translate on your calls and also it's
going to make you not feel good about yourself.
And so yeah it's not worth it like you know pushing yourself do something that
you don't like it's always good to try new things of course but if you're doing
something or you bother do something and you're very not feeling good about it.
And then just don't do it like just just you know just take the conversation
elsewhere or just with the conversation that clients.
It's not worth it because I've been there before I've done things on cam or you
know conversations when a certain way that I went comfortable with and I wasn't
.
I felt like I had to just go with it like back in the day before I realised
that I really don't.
Because even just shut your laptop or close them off like you don't have to do
anything you're not comfortable with and you're going to feel great after that
you didn't like you didn't push yourself you know.
And so yes that's what I have to say on that.
And I mean you're just going to end on building it, building this like a
business and treating it like a business rather than just like a little hobby
that you do on the side, even if it is just a hobby that you do on the side.
The more you treat it like a real business, the more it's going to pay you like
a real business.
And so as we mentioned earlier it's going to be consistent and if you can, if
you're in a position to plan more times you're going to go online, put it on
your profile and stick to it.
And obviously this is different to most jobs but the more you treat it like a
real job and a real business the more you'll get out of it.
And as well just set for as well you can follow over girls that are doing well,
like learn from learn from you know what you want to be calm or what your and
who's inspiring you.
And you can look at the overgills profiles in our group or just overgills on
the website or just overgills on Instagram or in general and learn from them
and go from there.
And do your own research as well, take full advantage of our members area and
you can watch YouTube videos, you can read blogs, you really want to train
yourself to be the best you can be like knowledge is power.
Yeah, you don't have to know every thing when you begin with, but the more you
learn about new things, the more it opens up and whole new world of old
different avenues you can go down.
For example, I know that I like to do domination I know that I like to do the
girlfriend experience I know that I like to talk about fantasies, like all
these different things you can go down so I've learned like different points in
each one.
And whereas if I just learned domination for example, then I wouldn't be able
to do different things so well.
And, and give this 110% and I promise it'll pay off.
So I wanted to talk about a little story quickly about one of our previous
members in a lady she, she comes to us and she was recently divorced and she
was left with debt left with a child like the child on her own support and she
didn't like have a job when she was with her husband.
You know she was like completely like what the fuck did we do.
And it was really inspired me this woman because she worked like she just was
on it like she was every day like laying a new thing to show me what she's
doing the profile just looked unbelievable she was amazing she really put so
much effort in.
And within a couple of weeks, I think it was probably a couple of months maybe
but seemed like very fast but probably a couple of months I'm not sure now it's
a few years ago, but I have very short space of time.
She paid off all the debt and put a deposit on her house for her and a son and
she was she just thrived like it was it was amazing but the one thing that she
really noticed is she put the effort in.
And that's that's all a tough she was you know she was any different to any of
those like it's not like she had this special talent or I don't know like to
succeed in this she just really put the effort in and it really inspired me the
thought well like she went after that.
And she took it so and it always does pay off if you put the effort in.
So, the in potential is basically, it's like the sky is the limit and if you're
naturally down to you if you put the effort in and put the time into your
profile and to yourself into your, you know, your knowledge and your, your
everything else and it definitely will pay off.
And final thing in don't like the bad days get you down or put you off.
It'll always pick back up again and if you never go online again and it's never
going to pick back up again you're never going to give it the opportunity to.
So just know that this is something that you have to accept with this job that
the will always be in times when it's not as busy times when like I've been
this a lot of times where I feel like oh my god like maybe I'm just done with
it now maybe I've been on the side too long and nobody wants
to see me anymore because I've been on there for like you know about many years
.
And I still have to doubt while I used to now I've kind of like snapped all to
that because I've seen that many times I just know it's going to pick up again,
but you probably will have to doubt, especially if you knew when it's dead or
when it's not busy for you.
And, but it will always pick back up again like you just need to keep at it you
just need to keep consistent.
And, yeah, it's not the best when you go on there and you're not making much
money, but it will pick back up and the money will come for sure.
So yeah, there's my points.
Do you want to go ahead well.
Yeah, I just, I just, I'm on the thing like about bad days that we, you know,
we all have bad days we all have bad weeks sometimes and even though you know
those of us that have been off in years and you know at times have been making
a lot of money.
We all go through that stages don't wait I mean I went through several stages I
've probably tuned your, tuned your ear up so many times you've been like, I
just don't know what's happened is there a problem with the site is it me like
what's.
And yeah, it just it always comes back and I think it can sometimes trigger
like a limiting belief in yourself, it can be like, Oh, God, maybe I'm not
attractive enough or maybe I'm not this enough or that enough.
And just rather than blaming that on cam, having a look at what that means for
you because that is a limiting belief.
You know, we can, you know, Georgia and I, you know, George's got way more
experience than me in this, you know, we all started not knowing anything about
it, not knowing what to say, not knowing what to do like everybody starts from
that point.
And only when you overcome those limiting beliefs that you can take it to the
next level and be like, okay, it's not that I'm not attracted today I'm going
to do this this this and this I'm going to put these steps into place and this
is what I'm going to do when I'm not going to sit and, you know,
I'm going to nourish myself and take the time to do something different, you
know, and someone said to me the other day about the first, the first, or I saw
something it was like the first rule of being successful is to realise that you
're no different from the most successful people
are, it's like they're no different than anybody else, it's just that they've
not limited themselves and they've tried something different in every door that
like slams, you just keep trying trying trying until it really works.
Definitely, like touching on the limiting beliefs about money or about anything
really I used to have really bad, bad, bad limiting beliefs about money like
really bad like I used to have a bad relationship with money and after it wasn
't until like I barely looked at that
like fix that and fix I don't know if the word is but worked on that basically
worked on my limited beliefs that I started to make a lot more money and do
better like be better with money
and I think like just getting yourself in the right mindset like I believe like
every finishes energy and like vibrations and what you're putting off there you
're going to get back, you know, so just really try and put yourself in the best
mindset and know you're going to do well
maybe that's just the time for the universe telling you, okay now it's time for
you to work on your profile for two hours while you're sat waiting for calls or
now it's time to, you know, pay your nails and like do whatever it is that's
going to make you feel good while you're waiting for the calls
rather than like you said sitting in and dwelling because it can't be easy to
do that especially if like, you know, you're not having a good day on cam or a
good day in general
but always just switching and be like what can I do that's going to make me
more successful or make me happier or make me feel better about myself or
whatever it is and I'm sure that the two hours that you sat there without the
calls or however long it is
would be used for the better for the greater good, you know, yes, and I think
we bang on about like having a routine and going on at the same time it's like
if you can but I think it's good to remember that's maybe not the only thing
you're doing
like I always have my notes or a book or some financial or like other things
that I'm doing so that I'm using my time nicely I'm getting things done or like
treating myself or whatever if I'm not getting calls, do you not just sat there
yeah, I'm guilty of shopping online and then like getting calls and I should be
doing the opposite I shouldn't be spending the money so I'm not making it so
sometimes I do that, just sometimes
yeah, I was just going to say, as I'm doing this, I'm doing my normal job only
two days a week now as I'll know and just doing this the rest of the time and
actually I've been doing it really consistently
and I can make over £100 a day, if I'm consistent it's great and I can do that
and I know that I've proved it to myself over and over, but the moment that I
stop, it's a bloody nightmare, so I think last week it was I had a three days
of inconsistency
getting back into it for both me and my clients, it was so hard and it was
hardly ringing whereas usually where I've been so consistent, people have
obviously had obviously gotten used to my rhythm of working and then it was
like nothing and I really struggled
yeah, I think we've all been there, we georgia, like we always say that, me and
georgia always say if we've had a few weeks off for whatever reason it's
building it back up like starting over again isn't it?
Yeah, it can be, yeah, and my busiest times were when I was consistent, when I
was on, I pretty much could be consistent with what I was earning but that's
for me as well, yeah, most of the time
but also that's life as well isn't it, that's life sometimes we'll have stints
where we don't do it and that's okay, that's the nice thing about this like
group is that we understand and that's life sometimes
yeah, exactly, there's no pressure to ever be on all the time if you can't be,
like I haven't been on now for the past couple of weeks because I have my
family here over on and visiting me, so I didn't go online, so I'm going to be
in that same boat like building back up again
yeah, we've got this, yeah definitely, and also when I started out to the new
bies out there, when I started out it was just, you know, it took time but like
georgia said earlier, it doesn't matter if you don't have loads of reviews
because they love newbies, they absolutely love newbies as well so, and it just
gives you time to get to know people and build up those reviews and get to know
what you're doing and what your niche is, like I said
yeah definitely, like your only new ones, so take advantage of this time, like
I recently got made a new profile with a guy and that obviously was a brand new
profile so I was doing the whole, I knew on this even though I've been on the
site for eight years on with my solo one
they're like yeah this is my first night and I was like, I don't know, they
feel like they're fully doing it, like I actually enjoy doing that, but the
guys loved it, they loved that I was new and they loved that like I was a bit
nervous to maybe do something and whatever else and
yeah I'm still playing on the new thing on that profile because it's still not
really got any feedback, so just play on the new thing while you cut the new
card while you can, because you're only new once
and the couples thing is always a good idea isn't it, having a couples profile
with a friend or someone who's around, even if you're not together all the time
, I put my cam on at the photo shoot last time and I was just like showing Emma
one of the girls what to do because she hadn't been online before
and literally I've got so many calls and I've got people still now who I've
spoken to a few times since then because they were just like and all I was
doing was like this is where you kick them off, this is where this is where the
mic is, literally I was just walking it through it and they loved it, they were
like oh my god you're like training her up
yeah yeah it's really good to be with other people isn't it, definitely,
because I'm on the couples profiles too, if you do make a joint profile with
one of your friends or a partner or whoever it is, there's not many couples
online like if you have a look and play on couples
there's probably not even two rows worth of couples where there's countless
rows of girls, so there's a lot less people so you don't have to position from
page of course because you're already on there
and there's like one in ten and so you're one in ten rather than one in six
hundred say, so yeah you've got a lot more, I find the couples profiles can be
a lot busier because obviously there's a lot less couples on there
so yeah it's way different because you don't and as well you don't even have to
do anything like sexual or anything like that you know
when I used to live with my friends in Spain we'd just put it on and we were
getting ready for a nice house or whatever and they'd just love to see us
having a drink together getting ready and yeah it can be really innocent as
well
so that's something to think about everyone if you've got any friends or
partner or anyone, it's definitely worth doing, I mentioned this a couple of
weeks ago in the group but yeah
and if you've got any friends that can and you get together even if you haven't
got a joint profile you can just me and Kelly do so well and we just can
together even though we're separate like with both our laptops out
exactly so they have clients get to know like each of us as well because we
have very different profiles and very different like alter egos and actually we
've spent like a little bit of money or feet over before like if I'm not a nine
one of my guys but then that looks for her because they'll
they'll not they might think that we're together and the same like one of her
guys looks for me sometimes and is like oh are you with me and I'm like oh no
tonight they'd like to get like a 20 minute conversation out of him in a
private so
yeah that'd be like super worthwhile if you can do that yeah they'd love to see
you with your friends because I remember they would come my friends and me
separately and then say things like oh I spoke to blah blah yesterday and she
said this
oh she said this like and you know I'd be like oh did you say that cheeky boog
er and like shit like that like we knew what we were saying to each other but
with you were like not playing us off against each other as well it's so funny
yeah but not like in not like a nasty way just like you know no no at all but
like in like a little funny way like oh she said this about your or like yeah
Kelly Kelly will say oh seriously said like oh she's missing you at the moment
because she's not been up to stay and they're like oh no he'd like private
private called me the day before and he thinks that we're like he's he's paying
us against each other do you know what I mean like yeah yeah exactly they love
it
you love that yeah not in a horrible way at all like he's all done like in a
fun flirty way yeah exactly and it's fun for you too as well it's fun for the
girls that are doing it because it's nice to have friends or whoever that are
doing it and you
oh yeah he said this to me and you know talk about the clients and whatever
else and yeah it can be fun kind of but something that's ugly but you can't
do you want to say sorry for me I think it was just not from last time no I don
't know I don't know I don't know I'm still not there I don't know I'm sorry no
I'm not oh no I'm sorry guys okay I was just going to say as well about
we've got a couple of things coming up or a couple of things that we'll post in
the group this week and so we're going to start doing mental health Mondays so
every Monday we're going to have a bit of a focus on well being on mental
health so
we'll post like either like a meme or a motivational quote or something or a
task in the group on Monday mornings and then me and Georgia are going to be
available between 12 and 1 every Monday you'll be able to messages for a chat
so on WhatsApp
for a little phone chat or just a chat on WhatsApp or voice note or whatever
and so obviously that would be like you know first conversation like as many
people as we can do but we just want to like put aside an hour each week
yeah to just listen to you and it doesn't have to be can related just you know
if you feel in a bit lonely or you've got something that you want to talk about
and it's just we're here to listen and we want to give you a bit of time about
where you know you can capture that it doesn't have to be can related so
we're just about that in the group and who do you want to say about the
competition Georgia I know we haven't sorted out the details yet but yeah so we
've not sorted out the details fully but we've got a nice little competition
coming up with a prize that I would absolutely love to win myself
to win that actually is amazing but yeah we'll tell you more about that
tomorrow because I'll make a poster tomorrow and then we'll tell you more about
it because we haven't finalized the details yet but it's a good one
she was talking about the prize okay so the prize is going to be for well for
people really that are more interested in getting into Dom getting into Dom in
or finding out a bit more about their Dom side
so we've got Mistress Ivy who did the call with us before and she's a friend of
mine she's a professional Dom and she's amazing at what she does so she's going
to give a one-on-one coaching session for domination to whoever wins the
competition
so it will be a competition throughout February just with a few things you've
got to do you know easy things that hopefully you'd be doing anyway with Cam
and then yeah early in March she'll be having a once-one hour call over Zoom
with whoever wins
where you can give you some tips try and bring out your Dom side she's lovely
anyway and just guide you through how you can bring that in on Cam so that's
exciting yeah that's a good one I'm jealous of that prize
yeah she's amazing she's so good yeah well then we'll give you more details on
that tomorrow when we then we've got the poster and stuff and we also in the
gallant times call well yeah yeah yeah we thought that maybe you know it's
Valentine's Day and Fair so we were wondering what to do and we thought maybe
we could do a gallant times maybe we could add like a social
and just come together and have a bit of laugh and just yeah have a bit of a
social call so we'll put that out there this week as well and we'll post there
but maybe I'll ask a couple of different times to see who's available and what
times
yeah and then we'll we'll sort that this week so we've got that forward too
yeah okay and also yeah I just think if there's anything that use one girls and
I know we actually this sometimes it does anything that you want calls on or
any even competition
prizes or things like that or is that anything that you want from us just let
us know because we do these at the end of day for you so we want to use what
you want so yeah have a little thing if there's anything you want any calls on
or anything like that and we'll be happy to then organise something for you
and the mental thing as well I know we've mentioned it on a couple of calls I
just like wanted to mention that we have we are that is something that will be
doing soon isn't it it's just that we've had a big focus on the website and
other things up until now so it's only now
obviously George's family's been there for a couple of weeks so it's only like
now that we're starting to you know yeah if I don't Google I'd send off for
some time so we wasn't getting any new like a lot of new people through but now
we will be so now we'll be looking maybe to get a mentor because we wanted to
get more girls through there was no point to do beforehand
and so yeah that's something that we're going to be doing soon as well which is
exciting and yeah okay now it's not well that wraps it up yeah I think that's
everything yeah thank you girls for coming it's nice to see your faces
and thank you for all the input as well from everyone because we've got some
really good input there and say thank you for sharing
yeah all right ladies we'll see you very soon it's nice to see you all
yes and I'll miss your faces
we miss you too
so you care everyone bye lady bye bye